games2girls.com 2015-05-10

# Games2Girls - Privacy Policy

Games2Girls.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. Games2Girls.com does not collect any personal information.

Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc).

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).

We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

It is Games2Girls.com's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, Games2Girls.com will immediately disable and remove games in question.

Games2Girls.com site contains links to other sites. Games2Girls.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Last Updated on November 7, 2013

Games2Girls.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. Games2Girls.com does not collect any personal information.

Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc).

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).

We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

It is Games2Girls.com's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, Games2Girls.com will immediately disable and remove games in question.

Games2Girls.com site contains links to other sites. Games2Girls.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Last Updated on November 7, 2013
